HELLO, TWENTY - WONHEE
EPISODE 4
Hello.
BOUNCING WITH EXCITEMENT TODAY
GRAND ENTRANCE AS THE BACKDROP
Awesome.
Can you tell the viewers where we are?
Everland.
FROM THRILLING RIDES
TO PICTURESQUE SCENES
STRAIGHT FROM FAIRY TALES
A LAND OF FUN AND THRILLS
TODAY'S SHOOT TAKES PLACE IN EVERLAND,
THE LAND OF FANTASY
Today, you'll enjoy everything
this theme park has to offer.
I'M SO IN
But you'll have to earn it through work.
WORK
I'M OUT
Wonhee.
DESPERATE
But I want to ride the T-Express.
Being an adult means
dealing with responsibilities.
And they're too much to bear.
You'll work as a part-timer
- at a couple of rides here
- Okay.
to experience the harsh reality.
Wow, I'm already loving this.
Do you want to call your partner
for the day?
Girlie.
Eunchae.
ADORBS
- Eunchae.
- It's been so long.
EUNCHAE OF LE SSERAFIM
Welcome. How have you been?
You must be busy promoting your new song.
Yes, we're pretty busy.
Still, I had to come
because I've never been
on a variety show with you.
- I've been looking forward to this.
- Me too.
Do you enjoy rides?
Not at all.
Oh, no.
THIS 21-YEAR-OLD IS FRIGHTENED OF THEM
I don't enjoy them.
The rain is mirroring my mood today.
You poor thing.
Please change into the uniforms
before your shift.
So cute.
It's all green.
GROOVING
LET'S GET OUR ENERGY UP
BEFORE OUR SHIFT BEGINS
- Are you ready to get changed?
- Yes.
Let's go.
- Over there.
- Okay.
- Let's do this.
- All right.
- We've got this.
- Sure.
Do you prefer your left side
or your right side?
- My right.
- Nice, I prefer my left.
EXCITED SQUEALING
WILL THIS PAIR DO A GOOD JOB TODAY?
- Wow, look.
- This is it.
It's my first time.
FIRST WORK SITE, T-EXPRESS
NOW CALLED MONIMO RUSH
HERE COME THE GIRLIES
- Hello.
Welcome.
Hello.
JAZZ HANDS
I'm Jang Hye-yeong,
a ride operator for T-Express.
- It's nice to meet you.
We have a set of tasks to complete
before guests arrive.
- Let me give you a briefing.
- Okay.
What do we have to do?
First off,
we'll check beneath the ride
for lost items
- and pick up any trash.
- Okay.
Next, we'll check the lap bars
to ensure our guests' safety.
- You will test their condition.
- Oh, really?
Do we perhaps go on the ride, too?
It's raining today, so...
GETTING HER HOPES UP
I don't enjoy them.
PLEASE...
But I want to ride the T-Express.
But if it stops, you can.
- Okay.
- Great.
THEIR REACTIONS ARE POLAR OPPOSITES
Congrats.
- Shall we, then?
- Yes.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
LET'S GET TO WORK
STEP 1
CLEAN THE AREA UNDER THE RIDE
When we cross the track,
we have to stick to the yellow lines.
Follow me.
This way.
It's slippery. Watch your step.
When we enter the area under the tracks,
we must wear a safety helmet.
- Please take one each.
- Okay.
PUTTING THEM ON
Make sure to fasten the strap.
SAFETY HELMETS ON
Great.
Now, let's go.
- Okay.
- Great.
Let's go.
OFF TO THEIR FIRST TASK
We're currently under the tracks
of the roller coaster.
As you can see, there's trash here.
We have to collect them.
We often find guests' missing items
such as cell phones,
lip products, and heat packs.
They should've left them on the platform.
That's right.
We always encourage them to leave
their belongings on the platform.
It's cleaner than I thought.
- I found a phone case.
- That looks like...
- It's for an older model.
- Right?
It looks like the back cover
of an older model.
I don't think
the owner will return to get it.
- Right.
- Yes.
If the owner is likely
to come back to get it,
- do we keep them elsewhere?
- Yes.
We can hold on to them
before handing them over
to lost-and-found.
I found a hand mirror.
- It's broken. Be careful.
- A mirror.
Oh, it's cracked.
COLLECTED THE BROKEN MIRROR
Let's go.
I thought there would be
more lost items here.
A section with more lost items
is actually up ahead.
- Is it the prized section?
- Yes, the one at the start.
- The steep dive early on.
- Oh, I see.
That's where many people drop their items.
- Be careful not to hit this beam.
- Okay.
- Look, we've got a credit card.
- A credit card?
- We should check the owner's name.
- Let's use that.
- Whose card is it?
- Tell us.
- "Cho Ha-yeon."
- Cho?
- Ms. Cho Ha-yeon.
- Why didn't you come back for it?
- You shouldn't have put it in the pocket.
Could we perhaps use it
to get some snacks later?
Hang on, I found a Pokémon card.
- A Pokémon card?
- Which Pokémon is it?
PLEASE LEAVE POKÉMON CARDS AT THE PLATFORM
"Duraludon."
You fit right in.
What does that even mean?
- Just perfect.
- Thanks.
Good job.
ENDLESS CLEANING
WONHEE AND EUNCHAE HUSTLE
- I found another Pokémon card.
- What?
They must belong to the same person.
I'll go to the other side to get it.
I guess we should.
We can go through here.
- Please watch your heads.
- Okay.
Be careful.
- Oh, dear.
- Please be careful.
UP ABOVE, THE TRAIN WHIZZES BY
Wow, that looks so fun.
Tell the world I'm not riding that.
She won't be riding it.
- Eunchae refuses to go on it.
- I just can't.
FEARS ASIDE, THEY GET BACK TO CLEANING
Is it coming this way?
Does the train have just one drop?
- There are 12 drops in total.
- What?
A whopping 12 times?
We'll now go check the lap bars.
You can go on the test ride to confirm...
...to confirm its safety.
- Okay.
You'll ride it, right?
PROTECT EUNCHAE
Eunchae, I'm sorry.
- Sorry.
- Tell her, Wonhee.
For the guests' safety--
I'm down!
WONHEE'S BETRAYAL
Great. Let's move, then.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
I get to work at Everland,
all thanks to you.
OFF TO CHECK THE LAP BARS
SAFETY IS A MUST FOR THRILLING RIDES
ALL THE LAP BARS MUST BE CHECKED
ONE BY ONE
STEP 2
CHECK THE LAP BARS
In the morning, all the levers are raised.
We'll lower the lap bars
just as we do when we have guests.
Before that...
- Clear.
- Once the order is given,
- put your body weight to lower them.
- Our body weight?
Otherwise, it'll put
too much strain on your arms.
So make sure to use your body weight.
- Try it yourselves.
- Okay.
- I'm a dummy.
- You'll wear your arms that way.
- Really?
- It's better
to push down with your body weight.
- So I should lean forward.
- Like this.
- Like Michael Jackson, right?
- Yes.
Like this.
Yes, that's correct.
- Great.
- You're hilarious.
WONHEE JACKSON
Like...
That's perfect.
It takes longer than I expected.
- Actually, you have to go faster.
- Really?
We fly through these.
WE WILL ALSO MOVE FASTER
Good job.
LAST LAP BAR CHECKED
I'll lower the bars on the other side.
- Can we see how fast you go?
- Do you want a demonstration?
- Of course!
- I can do this really fast.
HIGH ANTICIPATION
SPEED ON ANOTHER LEVEL
- You're so quick.
- You'll need a hearty breakfast
- before coming to work.
- Definitely.
As newbies, we had no idea
- and skipped breakfast.
- Right.
CLEARED IN NO TIME
We were saving room for the food here,
so we skipped breakfast.
Our cafeteria has great food.
I heard the staff cafeteria was amazing.
That's true.
Now, let's send the train on a test run.
This button right here starts the train.
We call this top button "Yellow."
Over there on Post 1,
there is a button
just like the one here at Post 6.
When all ride operators
stand behind the yellow line
after confirming the guests' safety,
we hold one hand up
as an all-clear signal.
After that, we press the buttons together.
When the control operator says,
"The train is ready to go,"
we push the green button
- with our hand up.
- "Go."
- Go.
When you push the button,
the train will leave the platform.
While the train is running,
we need to wave and observe it
to check the guests' safety
with one hand on the station stopper.
The moment you realize
the guests are in danger,
you flick it
- to stop the train.
- Just like that?
- Let's send this train on its course.
- Okay.
Should I take the other post?
WONHEE GOES TO POST 1
Great idea.
Please take on Post 6.
Once you confirm
that everyone is fastened securely,
raise your hand...
THROWS HER ARM UP
...and push the yellow button.
The sound just now means
the train is ready to go.
It's the control operator's turn.
The train is ready to go.
Go!
THE GREEN BUTTONS HAVE BEEN PUSHED
THE TRAIN DEPARTS SMOOTHLY
The T-Express train
has left for a test run.
- If you're close to...
- See you.
DON'T FORGET THE JAZZ HANDS
She's so cute.
If you're close to the lift or the tracks,
please move to a safe area.
The T-Express train
has left for a test run.
SAFETY CHECK COMPLETE
Thank you so much for your hard work.
When the train returns,
we can go for a test ride.
EXCITED WONHEE
Congrats, Wonhee.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING, EUNCHAE?
WE'RE RIDING IT TOGETHER
Gosh, this is nuts.
I can't handle this.
- I don't want to.
- You can skip it if it's too much.
No, I have my pride.
I'm 21, for crying out loud.
You turned 20 this year.
Let's celebrate it
with a roller coaster ride together.
You're the best.
- Have you seen anyone more loyal than me?
- Of course not.
You're the best.
- I'm calling myself loyal.
- But you deserve it.
- I'm such a devoted friend.
- Of course.
- Can we get on it?
- Yes.
- This is wild, Eunchae.
- Let me get this for you.
Honestly, I couldn't be happier.
I never imagined I'd be riding this
for the first time with you.
This is my first time, too.
- I'll never forget this cold seat.
- Let's rely on each other.
- I'll lower the lap bar now.
- Okay.
- There. You can't leave now.
- So cute.
- Wait, why is it too low?
- Here you go.
Shouldn't it be up here?
I really don't like this.
ABOUT TO FAINT
Thank you for doing this with me.
Hit the buttons to dispatch the train.
WE'RE READY
I can't tell if I'm shaking
from the cold or the nerves.
The T-Express train
has left for a test run.
SEE YOU, EUNCHAE
SEE YOU SOON
You've got this.
POLAR OPPOSITE REACTIONS
- So cute.
- Hold on.
You've got this.
What am I looking at?
Is this the first 77-degree drop?
That's correct.
MAX SPEED: 104KM/H
MAX VERTICAL ANGLE: 77 DEGREES
Okay, here I go.
DEJECTED
In a few seconds,
we'll reach the highest point.
DEAD EYES
Once we do,
the train will hit
a 77-degree drop at full speed.
This is nuts.
This is ridiculous.
It's almost a 90-degree drop.
All right.
Please make sure
I'M HOLDING WONHEE'S HAND
to hold the lap bar.
- Not just yet.
- Oh, my.
RAGING INTERNAL CONFLICT
It's okay. This won't kill me.
We've reached the peak.
All right!
WE'RE PROTECTING THE GIRLIES
SCREAMS
I want to be rich!
I want to make a fortune!
When does it end?
When does this thing end?
This is the best roller coaster
I've ever been on.
IF YOU'RE HAPPY, I'M HAPPY
They took our photo!
- I'm an idol, for crying out loud!
- I'm an idol, too.
I'm an idol, too.
COMPLETELY DRAINED
Wonhee, congrats on turning 20.
Thanks, Eunchae.
Jazz hands, please.
MADE IT BACK SAFELY
That's a wrap
on your T-Express experience.
- Thank you.
- Seriously, thank you.
How was it for you?
ESPECIALLY DEEP SIGH
I can't even remember
the last time I rode a roller coaster.
Then again,
when would I ever get to try it with you?
Just by ourselves, no less.
It was a rare opportunity for me, too.
It's time to go to your next station.
NEW UNIFORMS
The colors are
- quite familiar.
- Amazon Express, right?
This one will be rough for me.
- Isn't everyone there so energetic?
- Yeah.
We have to step up
and prove our worth as idols.
Let's go prove our worth.
ON TO THE NEXT STATION
WITH PRIDE AS K-POP IDOLS
HYPED UP WITH NEW UNIFORMS ON
Don't we look better in this uniform?
It feels like we can get really goofy.
SILLY LITTLE DANCE
This time,
you will work at Amazon Express.
What is this ride famous for?
The dances?
One of the operators got famous
for her rap-like instruction.
THEY DON'T KNOW THE WORDS
THIS IS IT, RIGHT?
WHO KNOWS?
THEY PROBABLY MEANT THIS
On your left is the exit
as well as the drying zone.
Please exit slowly.
I get to work at Amazon Express?
Hello.
- Hello.
HERE'S THEIR SUPERVISOR
Welcome, it's a pleasure.
I'm Park Han-byeol,
a ride operator for Amazon Express.
It's nice to meet you.
Here's what we'll do today.
You'll learn the staff dance,
the highlight of Amazon Express.
Trust us. We're idols.
We've got this.
I have high hopes for you.
THEY WILL BE LEARNING THIS
Welcome to Amazon Express.
Let's begin our lesson.
First off, pop your hips like this.
EMBARRASSED
As you pop your hips,
- spin your hands like this.
- Pop them.
Move to the rhythm.
Groove to the rhythm.
Next, put your arms up.
MODEL STUDENTS
Up.
- Center.
- Up, center.
- Down.
THIS IS PRETTY FUN
"Welcome to Amazon Express."
Hey, that was great.
- Then--
- Can we act cute for that part?
Of course. You can wink or make a heart.
CUTESY FLIRT
IDOLS ARE DIFFERENT
When I say, "splash,"
- spread your arms like this.
- Splash.
Then we face the guests.
STRIKE A POSE
FATALLY CUTE
There you go.
You got it just right.
BORN TO BE ON STAGE
FINAL HIGHLIGHT
Cute and lovely.
LOOK AT HER EYES
REALITY CHECK
During that part,
act as cute as you want.
Give it your all, kid.
WE'RE IN THE SAME BOAT
Come on, no slacking off.
I'm 21.
JUST ONE YEAR APART
Don't be like that.
- You're cuter.
- You're the youngest of your team.
I'm not, you know.
Baby of the team!
YOU'VE GOT THIS
So cute!
You could totally take the spotlight.
Don't be ridiculous.
You're the host of this show.
Next is the highlight
where all of us dance together.
It goes like this.
Bring your hand up and point.
We'll pop our hips.
We'll go to the right.
One, two, three, four.
- Clap.
One, two, three.
- Rub your hands.
- Rub.
- One, two, three, four.
REPEAT
One, two, three, four.
One, two, three, clap.
Next, turn around.
FINISHING TOUCH
For the finish, arms up.
Turn around...
How many times do we repeat the dance?
- Four times.
- Four times?
Okay, thank you.
- That's it.
- Thank you.
So...
- Let's do a final check.
- Okay.
One, two, three, four.
Groove to the rhythm.
- Up and down.
- We're good.
THEY EXCEL AT THIS PART
...Amazon Express.
Now, the highlight.
- Cute and lovely.
EACH OTHER'S ONLY LIFE LINE
Cute and lovely, here comes an idol!
What was that?
2ND ATTEMPT
ENDING FAIRY
You're good.
YOU HAVE MY APPROVAL
- Shall we get going, then?
- Okay.
- I don't handle crowds so well.
- Me neither.
EVEN ON A RAINY DAY
AMAZON EXPRESS IS A POPULAR ATTRACTION
WILL WONHEE AND EUNCHAE BE ABLE
TO PUT ON A GOOD PERFORMANCE?
HIGH ENERGY AT AMAZON EXPRESS
On your left is the exit
as well as the drying zone.
Please exit slowly.
All right.
We have very special guests
joining us today as a surprise!
- Please welcome Wonhee of ILLIT
- You're a natural.
and Eunchae of LE SSERAFIM.
Here they are.
Welcome to the Safari.
Welcome, everyone.
CHEERS KEEP ON COMING
We'll proceed to our performance.
- Let's dance together.
- So many teenagers.
Please turn up the volume.
We welcome all our guests
with a welcome performance.
We'll begin right away.
TURNING ON IDOL MODE
Let's do this.
Let's move to the rhythm.
Groove to the rhythm!
Up and down!
SQUEALS
Welcome to Amazon Express!
...to Amazon Express!
Clap your hands like this.
All right, this is fun!
Let's do this twice!
Be bold!
With high energy!
All right, splash!
Next up is the highlight!
Cute and lovely!
Every beginning has an end.
All staff will be joining for the ending.
Everyone, this way.
MOVING TO THE CENTER
Let's play the song again.
THE GIRLIES ARE NOW CLOSER TO THE GUESTS
ONE LAST REHEARSAL
SO NERVOUS
Let's do this, come on!
CAMERA TRACKING THEM
JUST LIKE ON MUSIC SHOWS
And now,
let's bring the performance to a close.
Thank you, everyone.
I'm exhausted.
Did you enjoy our performance?
- Yes!
Is that all you've got?
Are you sure you enjoyed it?
ONE MORE TIME!
A round of applause
for our special guests,
Wonhee of ILLIT
and Eunchae of LE SSERAFIM.
THANK YOU FOR THE WARM WELCOME
Let's say goodbye.
WAVING UNTIL THE LAST SECOND
What did I just do?
SHIFT AT AMAZON EXPRESS ENDS
My mind went blank.
How was it for you?
That was more intense than I imagined.
I didn't expect to face such a big crowd.
I think I'll dream about this.
- It was an invaluable experience.
- You can say that again.
- It was so nerve-racking, too.
- Yeah.
It was nice seeing all the teenagers...
- Good job.
- Thank you for everything.
Great work.
MAJOR RESPECT
You're incredible.
MAJOR RESPECT AGAIN
You are amazing.
Thank you.
Are you hungry?
- Yes!
Why don't we go to the cafeteria?
- Finally.
- Shall we?
- Every bite is going to be worth it.
- Totally.
Let's go.
I hear your cafeteria serves amazing food.
Our cafeteria is incredible.
- Let's get our lunch.
- Sounds great.
- I'm ready.
- Yes.
THIS IS THE FAMOUS STAFF CAFETERIA
- Finally, it's lunch time.
- Yes, finally.
What a nice setup.
They offer three options today.
Everything looks so good.
- Can I take one?
- Yes.
EXCITING MEALTIME
I bet everything will taste incredible.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
WONHEE IS ALSO PICKING UP FOOD
We get dessert, too.
Right.
This is solid.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
SO HAPPY AFTER THE SHIFT
I can't wait to dig in.
It's finally lunchtime.
You did a great job today.
You too, Eunchae.
INTROVERTS OUTDID THEMSELVES
- We've earned this.
- Definitely.
- Bon appétit.
FIRST, A BITE OF SIDE DISH
YUM
GRINS
WONHEE TAKES A BITE AFTER EUNCHAE
This is the jjamppong soup.
- Awesome.
- Oh, my.
This looks so good.
Thank you.
So delicious.
HAPPY MEAL WITH EXTRA SNACKS
THIS IS IT
This cafeteria is amazing.
It's so good.
It was a great experience.
- Right?
- You know...
The ride operators are incredible.
I got so nervous
that I tensed up these muscles.
- They got numb and started to shake.
- Mine too.
How are you around strangers?
Aren't you good with people?
- I make an effort to relax.
- So it takes work?
It's not easy to open up to people.
My social skills improved
while working on Eunchae's Star Diary,
but I've gotten worse
after the show ended.
How long does it take
for you to make friends?
Personally, my standards are high.
I don't use the word "friend" lightly.
I'm like you on that point.
- Do you have any hobbies?
- Hobbies?
I do, actually.
The weather has gotten warmer,
so I've been enjoying
long walks by myself.
After dinner, I'd go out on my own
and take a stroll across Yongsan.
Sometimes after work,
I walk to the dorm on my own.
Back when I was really into walking,
- I used to walk to work.
- I do that, too.
Do you have hobbies?
I have a few.
I don't dig into one thing.
- You try bits of everything?
- That's right.
- Tell me more.
- Still,
I read books...
But it's so cringe to say that out loud.
How come?
It gives me the ick.
I don't want to sound pretentious.
Anyway, I lend books to people around me,
including my staff.
- So--
- Really? Lend me some.
- Of course, hit me up anytime.
- Are you sure?
What's your favorite so far?
I love thrillers.
I like thrillers, too.
I enjoyed Hunter With a Scalpel.
The title sucks you in.
- Sounds interesting.
- It's fascinating.
Have you gone to late-night screenings?
Adults can see late-night screenings
to horror movies.
I've gone to those,
but not for a horror movie.
I'm a big horror fan, though.
- My group members are also fans.
- The problem is,
my group members are not.
Come join us.
WATCH HORROR MOVIES WITH US
One time, I really wanted to watch
this one horror movie,
so I dragged everyone with me after work.
They don't like horror in general,
but they still came along.
But after the screening...
I guess it was scarier
than they had expected,
so they complained to me afterward.
I have that memory.
I love the genre.
I get scared, but I enjoy it.
- Same.
- Really?
I can't stay cool
- Want to catch one at night together?
- or stay unfazed...
I'd love to.
Really? That's a promise.
- Nobody would join me.
- All my members love horror,
- Seriously?
- except for Yunah.
That's great.
Nice, I'll join you guys one day.
PLEASE JOIN US
Awesome.
What was your life like at 20?
Weren't you at Kōhaku Uta Gassen
on New Year's Eve?
JAPANESE SHOW
- Yes.
- Me too.
But I wasn't legal in Japan.
I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN
I couldn't really enjoy it
while I was there.
I didn't get to celebrate as much
on New Year's Day.
- I was the same way.
- Right?
When I came back to Korea the next day,
- I had a drink with my parents.
- I did that, too.
I tried alcohol over a family dinner.
Still, those little things
made all the difference.
When my group debuted,
I was the only minor on the team.
Whenever we had a team dinner
or went out to eat together,
I was the only one
who couldn't order drinks.
So after becoming legal,
I was happy to be able to enjoy
our time together more.
It's pretty much the same with me,
but Iroha's still a minor.
She's feeling left out.
How cute.
But she'll be legal next year, right?
CONGRATS
So everyone in ILLIT will be legal?
That's just...
It rings so strange to me.
You're the youngest member of LE SSERAFIM.
If you could choose,
where would you fall in the age order?
I've always loved being the youngest,
but I've changed my mind recently.
Almost everyone
in new idol groups these days
is younger than me.
While looking at them, I've come to think
that it might be nice to have
one member younger than me,
just like you do.
I just want one younger member.
- So fourth, I suppose.
- Fourth?
I'd like that.
Who would you choose if you could make
one member younger than you?
Kazuha, all the way.
Kazuha.
3 YEARS APART
Kazuha and I are closest in age,
so we're really close.
When I monitor my group's web content,
I look most relaxed when I'm with her.
I think we could have a fun dynamic
if we swapped our ages.
I honestly can't picture other members
being younger than me.
What about you, Wonhee?
Three members were born in the same year.
MINJU, YUNAH, MOKA
The three of them are very tight.
- Because they're the same age?
- Yes.
I wonder what it would be like
to be the same age as them.
CHUCKLES
Same age as them?
What changed for you at 20?
Did you have to take on
more responsibilities?
I don't have as many people
reminding me about things anymore.
It felt like I had to manage
everything on my own.
- I just wanted to do well.
- Right, I get what you mean.
AGE 20 COMES WITH RESPONSIBILITIES
SNACK TIME IS A MUST
CRUNCH
A churro at Everland.
An Ever-churro.
WRAPPING UP THE DAY WITH SWEET SNACKS
How was your Everland experience with me?
Basically, I was new to everything.
But with you by my side,
every moment became
an unforgettable memory.
- Really?
- It was therapeutic.
I got to be outdoors
and meet so many people,
especially the cheerful teenagers.
LAUGHTER NEVER STOPPED
- We even danced.
- It was therapeutic.
TODAY FELT LIKE A NICE BREAK
Really? I'm so glad.
You got on the roller coaster
to celebrate my turning 20.
Could you give me advice as well?
I still can't believe you're 20 this year.
It's crazy.
How can this little cutie be an adult?
- You look 17 at most.
- "This little cutie"?
You're 20? My gosh.
FROM 21-YEAR-OLD TO 20-YEAR-OLD
Here's my advice.
My gosh.
About turning 20.
I'd been looking forward to it as well.
I couldn't wait to hit 20.
I even wondered,
"Why am I the only minor?"
I was that impatient.
But when I finally reached that age,
I developed a new sense of responsibility.
Nobody gave me the push,
but I felt that way on my own.
You might also develop it
and feel burdened by it.
If you do, shake it off
and be your usual self.
I hope you stay as cheerful as ever.
Thank you.
Congrats.
- Thank you.
- I can't believe it.
- I'll be cheering for you.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for coming.
- Hope all your dreams come true.
- I will.
- Go for them.
I will!
- Thank you so much.
- Great work today.
Thank you.
"I HOPE YOU STAY CHEERFUL...
Take care.
...EVEN WITH NEW RESPONSIBILITIES"
A NEW CHALLENGE FOR A HEALTHIER LIFE
BOXING
This feels easy. Maybe I have a talent.
TRAINING PARTNER
This is pretty cool.
EPISODE 5 GIRLIE
PATRICIA
It's not so bad so far.
THE GIRLIES TAKE ON BOXING
You're something else.
CHAMPIONS FROM AFAR
Hang on!
COMPLETE DISASTER UP CLOSE
What on earth?
HELLISH BOOT CAMP BEGINS
Coach, please!
This is just...
- Is it that bad?
- It's terrible.
- Just one more set?
- No way!
Pull it together, Wonhee.
ABOUT TO FAINT
You've got this!
How much longer?
- You have 1 minute and 27 seconds.
- Maybe 20 seconds?
WRETCHES
THE ROAD TO A HEALTHIER LIFE ISN'T EASY
WILL THE GIRLIES SURVIVE THE TRAINING?
Come on, Coach!
Subtitle translation by Jeongwoo Kim